Delta Heat is a drama, action film directed by Michael Fischa.
cop investigates the death of his partner in the swamps of Louisiana.
Enlisting the help of an ex-cop who lost his hand
to an alligator many years before.
Mike Bishop, played by Anthony Edwards.
Jackson Rivers, played by Lance Henriksen.
Vicky Forbes, played by Betsy Russell.
Tine Tulane, played by Linda Dona.
Crawford, played by Rod Masterson.
Bill, played by John P. Fertitta.
Delta Heat is a 1992 American comedy drama crime film
directed by Michael Fischa and written by Sam A.
The screenplay was originally written by Bruce Akiyama to be a
television pilot, commissioned by Sawmill Entertainment.
After producer Richard L.
Albert made The Forbidden Dance, he decided to hire writer Sam
Scribner to expand the script to feature length.
The tone is emotional.